Byungwoo Jeon

50, Sinchon-ro 28-gil, Seoul, Republic of Korea

📱+82 10 33641362 | 🗷 ipcs@korea.ac.kr | 🛠 rootyjeon.github.io/ | 🖸 github.com/rootyJeon | 🛅 linkedin.com/in/byungwoo-jeon

Research Interest

My research goal is to build a representation of the 3d world so that it can be used in real-time for real-world problems. To this end, I focus on (i) how to effectively reduce the computation and memory cost of 3d data and (ii) how to understand primitives in general in terms of neural networks.

- Self-supervised and Contrastive Learning
- Neural Radiance Fields
- Generative Models

Education

Korea University Seoul, Korea

B.S. in Computer Science & Engineering, Statistics (Double Major)

Mar 2020 - Current

Experience __

Algorithmic Intelligence Lab (ALINLAB), KAIST AI

Jeongja, Korea Mar 2023 - Current

Undergraduate Intern (advisor: Prof. Jinwoo Shin)

- Researched prompt optimization on Vision-Language Models
- Researched Self-supervised Learning on Label-free and Zero-shot Tasks
- · Researched Depth Estimation with Neural Radiance Fields
- Participated in the ALINLAB weekly group paper study (Paper reading & Implementation)

ARCREAL Gangnam, Korea

Research Intern (host: Prof. Jinwoo Shin)

Jan 2023 - Current

- Developed AI systems for medical equipment
- Developed segmentation projects
- · Researched several 3d vision topics

LIM Lab, Korea Univ. STAT Anam, Korea

Undergraduate Intern (advisor: Prof. Sungbin Lim)

Aug 2023 - Current

· Researched Diffusion models with Genesis Lab

Machine Learning & Vision Lab (MLVLAB), Korea Univ. CSE

Anam, Korea Jul 2022 - Dec 2022

Jul 2021 - Aug 2021

Undergraduate Intern (advisor: Prof. Hyunwoo J. Kim)

- Studied Open-Vocabulary Object Detection
- Studied Human-Object Interaction (HOI)
- Participated in the government policy supporting AI challenge team
- Participated in the MLVLAB weekly group paper study (Paper reading & Implementation)

M-Monstar Pangyo, Korea

- Developed a modular e-commerce management platform page using Laravel framework
- · Optimized and debugged the site, HAGO

Full-stack Developer

OCTOBER 10, 2023

Honors & Awards

Artificial Intelligence Grand Challenge

Seoul, Korea

Top 9 (8^{th} Prize) Oct 2022 - Dec 2022

- Developed AI for supporting the government policies based on natural language proceessing
- Developed query parser for pre-processing

Training

United Collegiate Programming Contest

Seoul, Korea

3 Problems solved

Jul 2021

Yonsei-NAVER CLOUD Data Science Course

Seoul, Korea

Completed financial engineering course

Feb 2021 - Jun 2021

Ranked Top 40 in Hackathon

Seoul, Korea

Oct 2023

Skills

LG Aimers

Programming

Python (PyTorch, TensorFlow), C, C++, SQL, PHP, Javascript, R, SAS

Miscellaneous

Linux, Firebase, Git, ŁTEX

Soft Skills

Teamwork, Problem-solving, Documentation, Engaging Presentation.

Extracurricular Activity

KUBIG

Member

Jul 2023 - Jul 2024

- · Lectured Mathematics and Statistics for Deep Learning
- · Participated in Computer Vision Seminar
- · Participated in Time Series Analysis Seminar
- Developed personalized animated-video service using diffusion models
- Participated as a pacemaker in Deep Learning Session of Professor Sungbin Lim, Korea Univ.

Google Developer Students Club

Lead Jul 2022 - Aug 2023

- · Lectured Machine Learning, Databases, and Algorithm courses for undergraduate students
- Developed stable diffusion crawling with text summarization project
- Developed Horang-Studio, personalized AI profile service
- Developed 2023 Google Solution Challenge project (digiHow)
- Lead three teams to the Global Top 100 in 2023 Google Solution Challenge
- Lead one team to the Global Top 10 in 2023 Google Solution Challenge
- · Host of 2023 East Asia GDSC Global Hackathon in Tokyo

Korea Computer Science Academy (Academy club in Korea Univ.)

Member & Instructor Mar 2020 - Mar 2022

- Lectured Data Structure course for undergraduate students
- · Lectured C Programming course for undergraduate students

Languages.

English Korean Native proficiency

Professional proficiency

OCTOBER 10, 2023

Coursework_

2020-1	Fundamentals of Data Science	
2020-2	Computer Programming	
2020-2	Probability and Statistics	
2020-2	Data Structure	
2021-1	Algorithm	
2021-1	Theory of Computation	
2021-1	Discrete Mathematics	
2021-1	Linear Algebra	
2021-2	Databases	A+, Second-place
2021-2	Computer Network	
2021-2	Computer Architecture	
2022-1	Statistical Mathematics	
2022-1	Introduction to Probability Theory	
2022-1	Operating Systems	
2022-1	Artificial Intelligence	A+
2022-2	Machine Learning	A+
2022-2	Deep Learning	A+
2022-2	Regression Analysis	
2022-2	Probability and Random Process	
2023-1	Analysis	
2023-1	Natural Language Processing	A+
2023-1	Computer Vision	A+
2023-1	Statistical Data Science	A+, First-place
2023-2	Numerical Analysis	
2023-2	Introduction to Bayesian Statistics	

OCTOBER 10, 2023 3